Hirsh Health Sciences Library Records UA225
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Slide library, 1893 -- 1998; UA225.004; 1.2 Linear Feet; 937 Digital Object(s)
  - Medical Students, Curriculum, Tuition, Financial Aid, Match and Commencement, 1929 -- 1993; UA225.004.001.00002; Tufts University School of Medicine
    - tuition level comparisons, UA225.004.001.00002.00160; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Medical education--Statistics; Tuition; Georgetown University; George Washington University; Boston University; New York Medical College; Ponce School of Medicine; Universidad Central Del Caribe; Chicago Medical School; University of Pittsburgh; Tulane University; Tufts University School of Medicine; Medical College of Wisconsin; Slides (photographs)
    - Median tuition and fees, 1986 -- 1988; UA225.004.001.00002.00161; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - U.S. tuition public/private, 1988 -- 1989; UA225.004.001.00002.00162; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Academic Year 1988-89
    - tuition level comparisons, 1988 -- 1989; UA225.004.001.00002.00163; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Medical education--Statistics; Tuition; Georgetown University; Boston University; George Washington University; New York Medical College; Chicago Medical School; Tulane University; Ponce School of Medicine; Universidad Central Del Caribe; Tufts University School of Medicine; Baylor College of Medicine; Cornell University; Harvard University; Yale University; Slides (photographs)
    - tuition comparisons, 1989 -- 1990; UA225.004.001.00002.00164; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Academic Year 1989-90
      Medical education--Statistics; Tuition; Chicago Medical School; George Washington University; Tufts University School of Medicine; Georgetown University; New York Medical College; Tulane University; Baylor College of Medicine; Dartmouth College; Cornell University; Brown University; Harvard University; Slides (photographs)
    - tuition comparisons, 1990 -- 1991; UA225.004.001.00002.00165; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Academic Year 1990-91
      Medical education--Statistics; Tuition; Chicago Medical School; Georgetown University; George Washington University; New York Medical College; Boston University; Tufts University School of Medicine; Baylor College of Medicine; Tulane University; Dartmouth College; C; Slides (photographs)
    - tuition comparisons, 1991 -- 1992; UA225.004.001.00002.00166; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Academic Year 1991-92
      Medical education--Statistics; Tuition; Chicago Medical School; Boston University; Tufts University School of Medicine; George Washington University; Tulane University; New York Medical College; Georgetown University; University of Southern California; Northwestern University; Cornell University; Brown University; Harvard University; Slides (photographs)
    - Tufts tuition, 1982 -- 1993; UA225.004.001.00002.00167; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Academic Year 1982-1993
    - Tufts tuition, 1984 -- 1991; UA225.004.001.00002.00168; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Academic Year 1984-1991, "Tuition and Sponsored: % of Total Income"
    - Tufts tuition, 1984 -- 1991; UA225.004.001.00002.00169; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Academic Year 1984-1991, "Tuition and Sponsored: % of 'Net' Actuals"
    - Financial aid, UA225.004.001.00002.00170; Tufts University (Box 1)
      "Financial Aid"
    - Financial aid data, UA225.004.001.00002.00171; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Financial aid data: loan sources and amounts, UA225.004.001.00002.00172; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Loans
    - Indebtedness of M'83 financial aid data, UA225.004.001.00002.00173; Tufts University (Box 1)
      M1983; Student aid; Debt; Slides (photographs)
    - Financial aid data: indebtedness of M'83, UA225.004.001.00002.00174; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Include average indebtedness of M1981 and M1982, Indebtedness of M1983 includes Tufts, Boston University, Harvard, Umass, and national
    - Financial aid data, 1983 -- 1985; UA225.004.001.00002.00175; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Loans from 1983-1984 and 1984-1985
    - Financial aid data, 1984 -- 1985; UA225.004.001.00002.00176; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Loans from 1984-1985
    - Mean debt of indebted medical school graduates, 1979 -- 1985; UA225.004.001.00002.00177; Tufts University (Box 1)
      AAMC Mean Debt of Indebted Medical School Graduates 1979-1985
    - Financial aid data, 1985 -- 1986; UA225.004.001.00002.00178; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Loans and Scholarships
    - Other financial aid resources, 1985 -- 1986; UA225.004.001.00002.00179; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Class of 1986 - debt summary chart, UA225.004.001.00002.00180; Tufts University (Box 1)
      M1986; Debt; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM financial aid data, UA225.004.001.00002.00181; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Types of loans and grants (federal, state, etc.)
    - Financial aid data, 1986 -- 1987; UA225.004.001.00002.00182; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Also mentions armed forces scholarships
    - TUSM financial aid data, UA225.004.001.00002.00183; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Loans, Grants, and Aid
    - TUSM loan funds, 1980 -- 1987; UA225.004.001.00002.00184; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Aid endowment and aid loan funds, 1980 and 1987
    - TUSM debt levels, UA225.004.001.00002.00185; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Average debt of indebted medical school graduates, 1981 -- 1988; UA225.004.001.00002.00186; Tufts University (Box 1)
      AAMC Average debt 1981-1988
    - Financial aid data, UA225.004.001.00002.00187; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Mentions armed forces scholarships and national health sevice corp scholarships
    - TUSM financial aid dollars, UA225.004.001.00002.00188; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Fiscal Year 1987-1988, Loans, scholarships, outside aid
    - TUSM HEAL loans, 1984 -- 1988; UA225.004.001.00002.00189; Tufts University (Box 1)
      1984, 1985, 1986, 1987, 1988
  - Presidents, Deans, Faculty, 1902 -- 1994; UA225.004.001.00003; Tufts University School of Medicine
    - Founders of Tufts university school of medicine, UA225.004.001.00003.00001; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Chipman, William R.; Dudley, Henry W.; Hall, Walter L.; Johnson, John W.; Nott, Albert; Thayer, Charles P.; Wheatley, Frank G.
    - Dean Joseph M. Hayman, UA225.004.001.00003.00002; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Deans (Education); Slides (photographs); Hayman, Joseph M.
    - Dr. Samuel Proger, UA225.004.001.00003.00003; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Proger, Sameul H.
    - Dr. MacMahon, UA225.004.001.00003.00004; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); MacMahon, H. Edward
    - Dr. MacMahon, UA225.004.001.00003.00005; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Looking through microscope
    - Dr. MacMahon, UA225.004.001.00003.00006; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Plaque
    - Dr.Nicolaos E. Madias, UA225.004.001.00003.00007; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Madias, Nicolaos E.
    - Dean Maloney, UA225.004.001.00003.00008; Tufts University (Box 1)
      On telephone
      Deans (Education); Slides (photographs); Maloney, William F.
    - President Jean Mayer, UA225.004.001.00003.00009; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Dressed at graduation ceremony
      Slides (photographs); Mayer, Jean
    - President Mayer, UA225.004.001.00003.00010; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Looking out window
    - President Mayer, UA225.004.001.00003.00011; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - President Mayer and Vice President Levy, UA225.004.001.00003.00012; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Mayer, Jean; Levy, Robert I.
    - Dr. Alton Meister professor of biochemistry, UA225.004.001.00003.00013; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Meister, Alton
    - Philip E. Meltzer, M'18, UA225.004.001.00003.00014; Tufts University (Box 1)
      M1918; Alumni and alumnae; Slides (photographs); Meltzer, Philip E.
    - Mitchell, George Washington, Jr., UA225.004.001.00003.00015; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Mitchell, George W., Jr.
    - Dr. Morehead, UA225.004.001.00003.00016; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Morehead, James R.
    - Dr. Abraham Myerson, M '08, Professor and Chairman of Neurology, 1922 -- 1940; UA225.004.001.00003.00017; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Dates 1922-1940
      M1908; Alumni and alumnae; Slides (photographs); Myerson, Abraham
    - Dr. Paul G. Myerson, Professor and Chairman of the Department of Psychiatry, UA225.004.001.00003.00018; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Myerson, Paul G.
    - Dr. Carol Nadelson, UA225.004.001.00003.00019; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Nadelson, Carol
    - Frederick O'Brien, M '11, UA225.004.001.00003.00020; Tufts University (Box 1)
      M1911; Alumni and alumnae; Slides (photographs); O'Brien, Frederick
    - Col. Fox and Dr. Paine, UA225.004.001.00003.00021; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Paine, Alonzo K.
    - Charles F. Painter, M.D., UA225.004.001.00003.00022; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Painter, Charles F.
    - Robert Paul, M.D., UA225.004.001.00003.00023; Tufts University (Box 1)
      X-rays
      Slides (photographs); Paul, Robert
    - The faculty, UA225.004.001.00003.00024; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs)
    - Faculty numbers, 1989; UA225.004.001.00003.00025; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Science and Clinical, part-time and full-time
      Faculty, Medical--statistics and numerical data; Slides (photographs)
    - Faculty awards and leadership, 1989 -- 1990; UA225.004.001.00003.00026; Tufts University (Box 1)
      1989-1990
    - Faculty numbers, 1990; UA225.004.001.00003.00027; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Academic year 1990, science and clinical, part-time and full-time
    - Faculty Stature, 1990; UA225.004.001.00003.00028; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Faculty Honors, 1990; UA225.004.001.00003.00029; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Awards, scholars, presidents
    - Faculty numbers, 1993 -- 1994; UA225.004.001.00003.00030; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Academic year 1993-1994, science and cinical, part-time and full-time
    - Alexander P. Aitken, M.D., UA225.004.001.00003.00031; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Aitken, Alexander P.
    - Alexander P. Aitken, M.D., UA225.004.001.00003.00032; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Irwin M. Arias, M.D., UA225.004.001.00003.00033; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Arias, Irwin M.
    - Irwin M. Arias, M.D., UA225.004.001.00003.00034; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Holding pipette
    - Henry H. Banks, M.D., UA225.004.001.00003.00035; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Banks, Henry H. (1921-)
    - Henry H. Banks, M.D., UA225.004.001.00003.00036; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Henry H. Banks, M.D., UA225.004.001.00003.00037; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Elmer W. Barron, 1930 -- 1941; UA225.004.001.00003.00038; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Dates 1930-1941
      Slides (photographs); Barron, Elmer W.
    - Dr. James M. Baty, 1942; UA225.004.001.00003.00039; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Dates 1942-
      Slides (photographs); Baty, James M.
    - Dr. Horace Binney, 1929 -- 1936; UA225.004.001.00003.00040; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Dates 1929-1936
      Slides (photographs); Binney, Horace
    - Dean Murray Blair, UA225.004.001.00003.00041; Tufts University (Box 1)
      At desk with papers, speaking to someone out of camera view
      Slides (photographs); Blair, Murray
    - Dr. Thomas Broderick, M '41, UA225.004.001.00003.00042; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Talking to two people
      M1941; Alumni and alumnae; Slides (photographs); Broderick, Thomas
    - Dr. Thomas Broderick, M '41, UA225.004.001.00003.00043; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Attilio Canzanelli, M '26 and Carl J. Canzanelli, M '59, UA225.004.001.00003.00044; Tufts University (Box 1)
      M1925; M1959; Alumni and alumnae; Slides (photographs); Canzanelli, Attilio; Canzanelli, Carl J.
    - Dr. Louis Caplan, UA225.004.001.00003.00045; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Caplan, Louis
    - Dr. Louis Caplan, UA225.004.001.00003.00046; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Seems to be in classroom, with model brain
    - Dean Cavazos, UA225.004.001.00003.00047; Tufts University (Box 1)
      At desk
      Slides (photographs); Cavazos, Lauro F.
    - Dr. Werner Chasin, UA225.004.001.00003.00048; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Chasin, Werner
    - Dr. Charles G. Child, III, UA225.004.001.00003.00049; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Tufts Professor of Surgery and Surgeon-in-Chief New England Center Hospital
      Slides (photographs); Child, Charles G., III
    - Dr. Richard Cleveland, UA225.004.001.00003.00050; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Seems to be sitting at desk
      Slides (photographs); Cleveland, Richard
    - Dr. Mayer and Dr. Cleveland, UA225.004.001.00003.00051; Tufts University (Box 1)
      At an event
      Slides (photographs); Mayer, Jean; Cleveland, Richard
    - Dr. Frederic Cotton, UA225.004.001.00003.00052; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Portrait, black and white
      Slides (photographs); Cotton, Frederic
    - Dr. Stephen Curry, UA225.004.001.00003.00053; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Sitting in a chair
      Slides (photographs); Curry, Stephen
    - Dr. Ralph A. Deterling, Jr., UA225.004.001.00003.00054; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Face picture
      Slides (photographs); Deterling, Ralph A., Jr.
    - Dr. Benjamin Etsten, UA225.004.001.00003.00055; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Etsten, Benjamin E.
    - Alice Ettinger, M.D., UA225.004.001.00003.00056; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Ettinger, Alice
    - Alice Ettinger, M.D., UA225.004.001.00003.00057; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Working with X-rays
    - Dr. Feingold, UA225.004.001.00003.00058; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Looking in child's ear
      Slides (photographs); Feingold, David S.
    - Martin H. Flax, M.D., Ph.D.--new professor and chairman of the department of pathology, UA225.004.001.00003.00059; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Flax, Martin H.
    - Martin H. Flax, M.D., Ph.D.--new professor and chairman of the department of pathology, UA225.004.001.00003.00060; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Looking in microscope with students
    - Dr. Ivan Franz, UA225.004.001.00003.00061; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo with machine "BMO-20N Hummingbird"
      Slides (photographs); Franz, Ivan
    - Morris Friedkin, Ph.D., Professor of Pharmacology, UA225.004.001.00003.00062; Tufts University (Box 1)
      With spectrometer
      Slides (photographs); Friedkin, Morris
    - Morris Friedkin, Ph.D., Professor of Pharmacology, UA225.004.001.00003.00063; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Bruce Gans, UA225.004.001.00003.00064; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Sitting at desk in front of bookshelf
      Slides (photographs); Gans, Bruce
    - *MISSING SLIDE* Dr. Sydney S. Gellis with incubator baby, UA225.004.001.00003.00065; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Sherwood Gorbach, UA225.004.001.00003.00066; Tufts University (Box 1)
      In lab, looking at vials
      Slides (photographs); Gorbach, Sherwood
    - Dr. Richard J. Grand, UA225.004.001.00003.00067; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Sitting in front of bookshelf
      Slides (photographs); Grand, Richard J.
    - Dr. Carl Granger, UA225.004.001.00003.00068; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Granger, Carl
    - Dr. Otto John Hermann, Surgent-in-Chief, 1932 -- 1946; UA225.004.001.00003.00069; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Hermann, Otto J.
    - Dr. Karen R. Hitchcock, UA225.004.001.00003.00070; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Hitchcock, Karen R.
    - Dr. George W. Holmes, M '06, UA225.004.001.00003.00071; Tufts University (Box 1)
      M1906; Alumni and alumnae; Slides (photographs); Holmes, George W.
    - Jerome P. Kassirer, M.D., UA225.004.001.00003.00072; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Kassirer, Jerome P.
    - Miss Geneva Katz, Director of the Boston Floating Hospital, UA225.004.001.00003.00073; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston Floating Hospital; Slides (photographs); Katz, Geneva
    - Dr. Robert Kennison, M '60, UA225.004.001.00003.00074; Tufts University (Box 1)
      M1960; Alumni and alumnae; Slides (photographs); Kennison, Robert
    - Dr. Joan King, UA225.004.001.00003.00075; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, looking at scan of brain on screen
      Slides (photographs); King, Joan
    - Dr. Louis Lasagna, UA225.004.001.00003.00076; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Lasagna, Louis
    - Dr. Louis Lasagna, UA225.004.001.00003.00077; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. William MacAusland, UA225.004.001.00003.00078; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); MacAusland, William
    - Dr. Kenneth Mac Donnell, UA225.004.001.00003.00079; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Mac Donnell, Kenneth
    - Dr. Louis Phaneuf, M '13, UA225.004.001.00003.00080; Tufts University (Box 1)
      M1913; Alumni and alumnae; Slides (photographs); Phaneuf, Louis
    - Dr. Cadis Phipps, UA225.004.001.00003.00081; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Phipps, Cadis
    - Dr. Morton Prince, 1902 -- 1912; UA225.004.001.00003.00082; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Prince, Morton
    - Dr. Samuel Proger and Capt. Frederick H. Hauck (astronaut), UA225.004.001.00003.00083; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, in group
      Astronauts; Slides (photographs); Proger, Sameul H.; Hauck, Frederick H., Capt.
    - Dr. Edward Rabe, UA225.004.001.00003.00084; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, examining patient
      Slides (photographs); Rabe, Edward F.
    - Dr. David Rapport, UA225.004.001.00003.00085; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Rapport, David
    - Dr. Richard Reindollar, UA225.004.001.00003.00086; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, group looking at vials
      Slides (photographs); Reindollar, Richard
    - Dr. Randolph Reinhold, UA225.004.001.00003.00087; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Reinhold, Randolph
    - Dr. Samual A. Robins, M '14, UA225.004.001.00003.00088; Tufts University (Box 1)
      M1914; Alumni and alumnae; Slides (photographs); Robins, Samual A.
    - Dr. Mark Rogers, UA225.004.001.00003.00089; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Rogers, Mark H.
    - Dr.Benjamin Sachs, M '21, Professor of Ophthalmology, UA225.004.001.00003.00090; Tufts University (Box 1)
      M1921; Alumni and alumnae; Slides (photographs); Sachs, Benjamin
    - Dr. Elio Schaechter, UA225.004.001.00003.00091; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, examining petri dishes in lab
      Slides (photographs); Schaechter, Moselio
    - Dr. Elio Schaechter, UA225.004.001.00003.00092; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Jane Schaller, UA225.004.001.00003.00093; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Schaller, Jane G.
    - Dr. Bernard Schwartz, UA225.004.001.00003.00094; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Schwartz, Bernard
    - Dr. Robert Schwartz, UA225.004.001.00003.00095; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, group doing labwork
      Slides (photographs); Schwartz, Robert S.
    - Dr. William Schwartz, UA225.004.001.00003.00096; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, reading book, "The Painful Prescription"
      Slides (photographs); Schwartz, William B.
    - Dr. Maurice Segal, M '32, UA225.004.001.00003.00097; Tufts University (Box 1)
      M1932; Alumni and alumnae; Slides (photographs); Segal, Maurice S.
    - Dr. John Richmond, M '76, UA225.004.001.00003.00098; Tufts University (Box 1)
      M1976; Alumni and alumnae; Slides (photographs); Richmond, John C.
    - Dr. Richard Shader, UA225.004.001.00003.00099; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Shader, Richard I.
    - Dr. Joseph Shortell, Surgeon-in-Chief, 1946 -- 1950; UA225.004.001.00003.00100; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Shortell, Joseph
    - Dr. Benjamin Spector, UA225.004.001.00003.00101; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Spector, Benjamin
    - Dr. A Warren Stearns, M '10, UA225.004.001.00003.00102; Tufts University (Box 1)
      M1910; Alumni and alumnae; Slides (photographs); Stearns, A. Warren
    - Dr. David Stollar, UA225.004.001.00003.00103; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Stollar, B. David
    - Dr. John F. Sullivan, UA225.004.001.00003.00104; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Sullivan, John F.
    - Dr. Raymond Sullivan, UA225.004.001.00003.00105; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Sullivan, Raymond
    - Dr. Russell Sullivan, M '18, Surgeon-in-Chief, 1950 -- 1954; UA225.004.001.00003.00106; Tufts University (Box 1)
      M1918; Alumni and alumnae; Slides (photographs); Sullivan, Russel F.
    - Drs. Barbara Talamo and John Kauer, UA225.004.001.00003.00107; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, looking at vials
      Slides (photographs); Talamo, Barbara R.; Kauer, John
    - Dr. Arthur Thibodeau, M '32, UA225.004.001.00003.00108; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo of children?
      M1932; Alumni and alumnae; Slides (photographs); Thibodeau, Arthur A.
    - Dr. Arthur Thibodeau, M '32, Dean Academy, 1924; UA225.004.001.00003.00109; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Arthur Thibodeau, M '32, Tufts Freshman, 1925; UA225.004.001.00003.00110; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Arthur Thibodeau, M '32, Tufts Football, 1926; UA225.004.001.00003.00111; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Arthur Thibodeau, M '32, Tufts College, 1928; UA225.004.001.00003.00112; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Arthur Thibodeau, M '32, Senior in Medical School, UA225.004.001.00003.00113; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Arthur Thibodeau, M '32, Norfolk State Prison Hospital, 1932; UA225.004.001.00003.00114; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Arthur Thibodeau, M '32, Norfolk State Prison Hospital, 1932; UA225.004.001.00003.00115; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Arthur Thibodeau, M '32, Intern at Worcester Hospital, 1933; UA225.004.001.00003.00116; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Arthur Thibodeau, M '32, Boston V.A., 1975; UA225.004.001.00003.00117; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, looking at scans (chest x-ray?)
    - Dr. Arthur Thibodeau, M '32, Boston V.A., 1975; UA225.004.001.00003.00118; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Arthur Thibodeau, M '32, BCH Staff, UA225.004.001.00003.00119; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, group
    - Dr. Arthur Thibodeau, M '32, BCH Alumni (1st row standing, 3rd from right), UA225.004.001.00003.00120; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Arthur Thibodeau, M '32, Fellow, Hospital for Ruptured and Crippled, 1937; UA225.004.001.00003.00121; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Arthur Thibodeau, M '32, Lt. Col. U.S. Army, 1945; UA225.004.001.00003.00122; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Arthur Thibodeau, M '32, UA225.004.001.00003.00123; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, with patient
    - Dr. Arthur Thibodeau and Portrait, 1980-01-23; UA225.004.001.00003.00124; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, standing next to his portrait
      Slides (photographs); Thibodeau, Arthur A.
    - Dr. Arthur Thibodeau and Portrait, 1980-01-23; UA225.004.001.00003.00125; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, with portrait
    - Dr and Mrs. Cavazos, Dr. Nalebuff, Matthew W. Boyhan (artist), Thibodeau portrait, Dr. and Mrs. Thibodeau, and Dr. Banks, UA225.004.001.00003.00126; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Slides (photographs); Cavazos, Lauro F.; Edward Nalebuff; Boyhan, Matthew W.; Thibodeau, Arthur A.; Banks, Henry H. (1921-)